<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <integer-array name="articles_paid">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="articles_titles">
        <item>Making Ratings and Reviews better for users and developers</item>
        <item>The Firebase guide to building stable, high-performing apps</item>
        <item>Android 12 Beta: Designed for you</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="articles_content_ids">
        <item>111</item>
        <item>222</item>
        <item>333</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="articles_url">
        <item>https://android-developers.googleblog.com/2021/08/making-ratings-and-reviews-better-for.html</item>
        <item>https://firebase.googleblog.com/2021/07/the-firebase-guide-to-building-stable-high-performing-apps.html</item>
        <item>https://blog.google/products/android/android-12-beta/</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="articles_text">
        <item>Ratings and reviews are important.
            They provide valuable quantitative and qualitative feedback on your users’ reported experience of your app or game, and the broader service that you offer.
            That’s why they’re one of the signals people use when deciding what to download on Google Play.\n\n
            We’ve heard from both Play Store users and developers that ratings and reviews could be more helpful.
            This is especially true when ratings from one area unfairly impact another —
            like when a bug that only impacted a single country negatively affects the app’s rating everywhere;
            or when positive improvements in a tablet experience are overlooked because of the number of users on phones.\n\n
            So we’re starting a multi-quarter program of improvements to make ratings more personalized and indicative of the experience each individual user can expect,
            and to make them easier to navigate and use for developers:
            We understand that many developers closely monitor the ratings that their potential users see,
            so we’re making sure you have plenty of notice about these upcoming changes.
            We’ve also made enhancements to Play Console to help you understand your ratings and reviews - especially across form-factors.\n\n
            Expanding your support for different device types is one of the most important and impactful changes you can make to your user interfaces.
            Adding tablet-optimized layouts or better mouse and keyboard support for Chrome OS can result in a step-change in the quality of your users’ experience,
            which in turn influences their ratings and reviews.
            To make it easier to spot opportunities across various device types and track the impact of enhanced experiences,
            we’ve added new Device Type dimensions to the ratings page.
            We’ve also added a Device Type filter to your reviews so you can easily see how your tablet users are rating you,
            or what your users on Chrome OS say in their reviews.
            Many of you have told us that you want to access more granular data than our selectors allowed.\n\n
            So, we’ve broken down your segmentation options and made them easier to use.
            You can now independently select the time period you want to plot (from the last 28 days through to your app’s complete lifetime),
            and how you want your ratings data to be aggregated (daily, weekly, or every 28 days). This allows you to access more granular data over longer periods of time.\n\n
        </item>

        <item>This is an introduction to a three part blog post series on app quality exploring how to unlock app stability and app performance for the optimal app experience.
            Find links to the other articles at the end of this blog post.
            Stability and performance are the core of every successful app. Fast, crash-free experiences encourage users to stay engaged and drive positive reviews.
            That’s why keeping a close eye on your app’s stability is crucial for competing in today’s thriving app marketplace.\n\n
            Why quality matters
            Users expect the best experience every time they interact with an app. And if bugs or latency issues get in the way, they’ll be quick to find a better option.
            Research has shown 88% of app users will abandon apps based on bugs and glitches.
            And within that group, 51% of users said they’d abandon an app completely if they experienced one or more bugs per day.\n\n
            Not only is quality important to retaining users, but it’s important for attracting new users as well.
            If a large percentage of users are frustrated and your app store listing is filled with negative feedback about performance issues,
            you might have trouble acquiring new users.
            In fact, 54% of users who left a 1-star review in the Play Store mentioned app stability and bugs
            A large portion of the pre-launch development for a new app is spent squashing bugs and testing for potential issues.\n\n
            But getting your app ready for launch is just the first step —
            once it’s out in the world, maintaining your app’s health becomes an ongoing process as you create new features and iterate on previous versions.\n\n
            </item>

        <item>From the beginning, Android has always been about personalization and allowing you to select the device, service and experience that’s right for you.
            By providing an open ecosystem that gives you choice, Android has grown to more than 3 billion active devices around the world.\n\n
            Android 12 builds on everything you love about Android, and focuses on building a deeply personal phone that adapts to you,
            developing an operating system that is secure by default and private by design, and making all your devices work better together.\n\n
            Today, we’re releasing the first beta of Android 12, and giving you a look into some of the features that will be available in future releases.\n\n
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>